================================================================================
FEATURE ANALYSIS TEMPLATE
================================================================================
Introduction
This document has been created to provide an in-depth Feature analysis document for a web-based application called the "Event Booking System". It begins by outlining the system's purpose and scope of the system. A Feature Analysis document provides a comprehensive overview of the features of a system. However, all the written features are set out according to the IEEE standards. 
Purpose
The primary objective of this document is to provide a detailed overview of the features for the "Event Booking System" project. The document is intended to aid project managers, business analysts, developers, and requirements engineers, as well as clients and other stakeholders, in understanding the system's functionalities, features, and requirements. Moreover, it will serve as a foundation for future system updates and the development of subsequent versions.
Intended Stakeholders
Product Owner
Business Analyst
Project Manager (Development Team Lead)
Developer Team
Testers (Quality Assurance Team)
Visitor
Registered User/ Attendee
Event Organizer
Super Admin
System Scope
The proposed system will be a web-based application designed to facilitate users to book tickets for events. A registered user will have the ability to search for organizers, view the latest events, and manage their profile, view all purchased (upcoming and expired tickets). A registered user can purchase events by adding necessary details. The organizer will have the facility to scan QR code to verify and mark the attendance of event attendees. Additionally, they will be able to manage event deposits and view analytics related to their e
Features
VisitorÆ Features
View FAQ section
View terms and condition section
Explore event section
Search Events
Apply filters on searched record
Get Event details
Get organizer details
Find organizers through search
Apply filters on searched record
View about us section
Get help from help center
View privacy policy
View testimonials 
View cookie setting
Attendees/ Registered User Features
Sign up
Sign up by submitting a form (name, email, phone number, password, and confirm password)
Sign up with Facebook
Sign up with Twitter
Sign up with Google
Login through (phone number and password)
Login with Facebook 
Login with Twitter
Login with Google
Forget password
View homepage
View latest event on home page
View category on home page
View featured event on home page
View testimonials
Manage Personal information (View, Add, edit)
View favorite event
Share on social media about favorite event
View following event organizers
Account Setting
Notification Setting
Change password
View transaction history
View all purchased tickets (upcoming event ticket and expired tickets)
Download upcoming tickets
Scan QR code for ticket
Search Events
Apply filters on searched record
Get event details page
Purchase ticket
Add Personal details (Name, email address, phone number and password)
Add payment methos to pay for ticket
Share on social media
View event organizer section/ page
View details by organizer
View all event by this organizer
Share event details on social media
Log out
Event OrganizerÆs Features
Login through Phone number and password
Forget password
View Dashboard
View total events analytics
View total earning details
View purchased events details
View total attendees/ customers
Create event
Add event information/date
Add event venue
Add total available tickets details
Manage ticket by price (View add, edit, delete)
Share on social media
Manage event details (View, add, edit, delete)
View attendees
Manage deposit details (View, add, edit, delete)
View all the tickets on the base of price
Scan QR code to check in attendees
Mark attendees
View analytics of events
View all the events sold ticket report
View all the event attendees
View organizer profile page
Manage personal information (View, add, edit)
View followers
Connect with social media
View transaction details (all earning details)
Account setting
Notification setting
Change password
Log out
Super Admin
Login through phone number and password
Forget password
View Dashboard
View attendeesÆ details
View event organizerÆs details
View event details
Manage registered user/ attendees (View, add, edit, delete, block, search)
Apply filters on searched record
Manage event organizers (View, add, edit, delete, block, search)
Apply filters on searched record
Manage FAQ section (View, add, edit, delete, search)
Manage terms and conditions page (View, add, edit, delete, search)
Manage Privacy policy section (View, add, edit, delete, search)
Manage help center (View, add, edit, delete, search)
Manage testimonials (View, add, edit, delete, search)
Manage pricing/payment methods (View, add, edit, delete, search)
Manage application social media accounts (View, add, edit, delete, search)
Manage about us section (View, add, edit, delete, search)
Manage personal information (View, add, edit)
Account setting
Notification setting
Change password
Log out
Advanced Features and Integrations
2.5.1 The system integrates with Bank for calculating money in/out
2.5.2 The system integrates with bank for refunds
2.5.3 The system integrates with bank for disputed charges
2.5.4 The system integrates with credit cards for fee calculations and processors
